[Music]
girl you really got me going you got me
so I don't know what I'm doing yeah you
really got me now you got me so I can't
sleep at night yeah you really got me
now you got me so I don't know what I'm
doing now oh yeah you really got me now
you got me so I got you really got
me you really got me you really got
there see don't ever Set Me Free I always
want to be by your side girl you really
got me now you got me so I can't sleep at
night yeah you really got me now you got me
so I don't know what I'm doing oh
yeah you really got me now you got
me so I can't see By Night You Really Got
Me You Really Got Me You Really Got Me Oh
[Music]
SE don't ever Set Me Free I always want
to be by your side girl you really got me
now you got me so I can't sleep at night
yeah you really got me now you got me so
I don't know what I'm doing oh yeah you
really got me now you got me so I got
By Night You Really Got Me You Really
Got Me You Really Got Me [Music]